<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Steven Korvin</title>
        <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/</link>
        <description>This is my personal website.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:22:42 -0400</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://stevenkorvin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Prioritizing Mental Health</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/prioritizing-mental-health/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:22:42 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/prioritizing-mental-health/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As I just posted on my Hashnode blog, I need to stay occupied with things that are meaningful to me. I&rsquo;m doing QubitxQubit&rsquo;s Quantum Summer School held in collaboration with IBM on Monday to Friday from 12 to 4 pm. I&rsquo;m also taking a COBOL class at Bergen Community College, also held in collaboration with IBM, on Tuesdays and Thursdays from 7 to 9 pm. Additionally, I&rsquo;m continuing with the Electric Vehicle Conversion project and I&rsquo;ll be on campus on Tuesdays and Wednesdays from 9 to 11 am. These things are all very healthy for me and they&rsquo;re things that I want to do.</p>
<p>In April of 2020, I had 1.44 BTC. How can I possibly HODL when I&rsquo;m as stressed as I was? COVID had nothing to do with that &ldquo;mistake.&rdquo; I tried to do something about my stress and in November of 2020, I bought a car knowing that I wasn&rsquo;t going to be able to pay for gas and insurance. I ended up selling the car.</p>
<p>I was about to start a data science menteeship with a mentor from MentorCruise. I suddenly became very busy, though, and I felt that it would be better for me to take things at my own pace.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m going to be prioritizing my mental health by staying productive.</p>
]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Things Are Continuing</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/things-are-continuing/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 01:48:15 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/things-are-continuing/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>The Community College Innovation Challenge was a very rewarding and tiring experience. Everyone says that it would&rsquo;ve been so much easier in person. They talk about &ldquo;Zoom fatigue.&rdquo; For me, it would&rsquo;ve been much more difficult in person. According to the Computer Science, Engineering, and Information Technology department&rsquo;s dean, our team&rsquo;s participation in the competition had created potential partnerships with Bergen Community College. The real focus of the competition was entreneurship. I&rsquo;m not well-versed in business, but I have a very good friend who is. She&rsquo;d be glad to potentially one day start a business with me.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ll be leaving the Electric Vehicle Conversion project for a month to participate in the Quantum Computing Summer School with IBM Quantum. Bergen Community College will be paying for the course&rsquo;s tuition, though I&rsquo;ll be paying $100 that&rsquo;ll be refunded upon completion of the course. I&rsquo;ll be rejoining the Electric Vehicle Conversion project this fall.</p>
<p>Last Thursday, the team working on the other project that I participated in last year at Bergen Community, the Ethical Hacking project, presented. They did an excellent job. I&rsquo;ll probably get a chance to be a student intern again next summer. If the project will still be running, then I think that I&rsquo;d like to rejoin it while continuing working on the Electric Vehicle Conversion project. This summer, I had to relax and prepare for the competition.</p>
<p>Starting on July 6th, I&rsquo;ll be participating in a mini-course provided by Bergen Community College named Introduction to COBOL Programming and System Z. July through mid-August will be busy for me!</p>
]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>My First Post</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/06/my-first-post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 01:07:48 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/06/my-first-post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>I wasn&rsquo;t into paying Squarespace to maintain a website, so I went with GitHub Pages and Hugo! It seems like it&rsquo;ll work. I already have a personal domain.</p>
<p>I had a very productive day on Friday. I was told that I &ldquo;looked very relaxed&rdquo; after completing my tasks that day. I need productive days more often and in order to experience them, I&rsquo;m going to apply for a job after this summer job with school will be over. Due to my productive day, I found myself able to give up fiction. Fiction makes me feel very sick; however, I&rsquo;ve kept consuming fiction because I&rsquo;ve been going stir-crazy. Without fiction, I&rsquo;d just be walking around my apartment all day. Consuming fiction has felt like a better choice than a day filled with pacing.</p>
<p>You might wonder what my productive day on Friday had entailed. Well, I went to campus as a recent graduate of Bergen Community College and I worked on the truck for the Electric Vehicle Conversion project that I&rsquo;m currently a part of. Our team got half of the truck&rsquo;s wheels turning! That was great progress! It was my first time seeing the truck. Campus has been off limits for so long.</p>
<p>These next two weeks will be work toward the Community Colleges Innovation Challenge that our team is a finalist in.</p>
<p>Otherwise, though, I bought a one-month subscription to TryHackMe for some infosec training and I started looking through O&rsquo;Reilly Media again. I have a subscription to it as a Bergen student. Yes, I&rsquo;ve graduated, but I&rsquo;ll be taking classes there during the upcoming academic year. I also bought a one-month subscription to Inoreader Pro so that I can look through my RSS feeds again. I&rsquo;m very satisfied with the various actions that I&rsquo;ve set up with IFTTT Pro to send things to OneNote.</p>
]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
