<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>family - Tag - Steven Korvin</title>
        <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/tags/family/</link>
        <description>family - Tag - Steven Korvin</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 18:54:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenkorvin.com/tags/family/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>I Am Sure Trying</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/i-am-sure-trying/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 18:54:47 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>steven-korvin</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/i-am-sure-trying/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As the title says, I am sure trying. Admittedly, each day is a struggle. I try so hard. I&rsquo;ve been accused of not trying, but I&rsquo;ve been trying each day of my life.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve been doing good work on the Electric Vehicle Conversion project and our faculty mentor on the project knows that I&rsquo;ve been under a lot of stress. He really appreciates that I&rsquo;ve been trying so hard, that I&rsquo;ve been willing to contribute in any way that I&rsquo;ve been able to, and that I&rsquo;ve always been willing to learn new things during my work on the project while I&rsquo;ve been stressed.</p>
<p>He&rsquo;s certainly willing to provide a recommendation for Stevens and this fall, he&rsquo;d like to talk to me about my plans for Stevens and my career plans.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve been feeling very tired from Quantum Summer School. It hasn&rsquo;t been the material that has been exhausting me, but it&rsquo;s been the jokes, the memes, and the chat. The chat has been horrific for me. There are over 200 people from all over the world in Quantum Summer School.</p>
<p>The video game repair company that I applied to was interested in talking to me, but ultimately, I couldn&rsquo;t get the job because I wouldn&rsquo;t have had enough work hours for training.</p>
<p>Here is a Reddit post of mine in which I describe how much difficulty I&rsquo;ve been having: <a href="http://link.stevenkorvin.com/9mtNjw" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">http://link.stevenkorvin.com/9mtNjw</a></p>
<p>I was a bit talkative during my COBOL class today. It was because I&rsquo;ve been exhausted. Because Bergen Community is rolling out multi-factor authentication,I had explained my previous process of writing the backup codes from the sites that had supported them on business cards and putting them in a wallet. Also, I had maintained a local password manager database using KeePass. It wasn&rsquo;t long before that had failed on me. Now, I keep everything like that in 1Password.</p>
<p>After that, the professor had asked if anybody has used hardware security keys. I showed him my Yubikey 5 NFC and my Google Titan key on my keyring. I then talked about my Trezor T, which I keep in my apartment and the MicroSD card  that I keep in my wallet that has the microcontroller unit&rsquo;s decryption key on it. The professor asked &ldquo;What happens if you lose THAT?&rdquo; I then explained that you wipe the device and you set it up again using your paper backup.  He then said &ldquo;Okay. That makes sense!&rdquo; Cryptography is so awesome. I also talked about how the Trezor T became useful when I had accidentally thrown my keyring in the dumpster last year because of stress.</p>
]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Something to Let Out</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/something-to-let-out/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 18:40:43 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>steven-korvin</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/something-to-let-out/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>This is going to be a no holds barred post. In the past, I had worried about what my family might think regarding my posts about prioritizing my mental health.</p>
<p>I feel so much stress. This is not new. I have been feeling this for a very long time, perhaps, all my life. I&rsquo;m so fortunate to now have my own apartment. I just wish that I could drive. I don&rsquo;t wish that to have a social status or to hang out with friends. I don&rsquo;t wish it to go to events. I just wish that I wasn&rsquo;t trapped in my apartment.</p>
<p>For nine years, I had begged my parents for a car. Each time, I had gotten a new response. Each response was a deflection. Of course, one of those responses had been &ldquo;You want a car so bad? BUY ONE YOURSELF!&rdquo; After nine years, I did just that with an ABLE account. My mother&rsquo;s reaction to my car purchase had made me afraid for my life! After one day, I began looking to sell the car.</p>
<p>Please keep in mind that the car purchase was something that I had planned for months. It wasn&rsquo;t a spur of the moment decision. I worked for months to get my credit repaired. Getting my credit repaired involved many phone calls, a fax at Staples, and a trip to the hospital to receive my discharge papers. After my credit was repaired, I bought the car.</p>
<p>Going back a year prior, I had a once in a lifetime opportunity by getting FREE MONEY from my school. I ruined it. I don&rsquo;t care about most consumer items. It&rsquo;s not a philosophy. Most consumer items don&rsquo;t interest me. I bought such stupid things, though, and I repeated the process several times of buying and selling those items. The stress was unbearable.</p>
<p>The other component to my stress was that everything had felt so far away. I plan to apply to the Stevens Institute of Technology early next year and I still had a lot of difficult work to do to be able to apply. I had to take Pre-Calculus, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry, and Biology! Thankfully, I&rsquo;ve taken three of those classes and I&rsquo;ll be taking Chemistry this fall. That will allow me to apply early next year. I&rsquo;ve been trying so hard.</p>
<p>The circumstances that led me to get kicked out of NJIT no longer exist. I will be able to succeed at Stevens. I have my own apartment and I&rsquo;ve learned about my eligibility for the Total and Permanent Disability Discharge. Also, I&rsquo;ve been able to process all of the trauma from before I had left for NJIT.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s not just that I&rsquo;ve been stressed while doing nothing. I&rsquo;ve been working so hard. This is not a COVID-related issue. 2020 was very stressful for me, but it was an excellent year for me compared to other years. COVID had nothing to do with what I was feeling.</p>
<p>When I was at NJIT, I had taken Greyhounds in an attempt to deal with my stress. The Greyhounds had been very effective. When my mother had taken me out of the city and into the suburbs, I had felt such a relief. When I was at NJIT and when I was in the hospital, I had made a car the crux of my argument as to what could&rsquo;ve been done about my stress.</p>
<p>My brother had gotten a brand new Chevrolet Equinox as a graduation gift while I was stuck in my parents' house. Of course, my parents think that I&rsquo;m inhrerently unable to drive. My mother takes me out for drives nearly every day and that&rsquo;s done more than you can imagine for my stress.</p>
<p>My mother is under so much stress, too. If you put two and two together, wouldn&rsquo;t it be less stress for my mother if she had just my father to deal with? It&rsquo;s her choice to take me out for those drives, but she drives me to and from more pressing matters. She even cancels and postpones appointments to make that happen.</p>
<p>I had 1.44 BTC in April of 2020. It wasn&rsquo;t that I was shortsighted. I just couldn&rsquo;t take my stress. In February, I started getting to know my friend Asha who lives in central New Jersey. She has really helped as far as my stress has gone. Today, I saw news on Cointelegraph that Amazon plans to accept Bitcoin this year. Getting back to 1 BTC was a pipe dream.</p>
<p>I can&rsquo;t blame myself, but at the same time, this could&rsquo;ve been prevented. My mother&rsquo;s reactions in late 2019 hadn&rsquo;t helped, either. She had stolen my first school refund check! She had returned it after a month of pleading from me. Then, in December, when it was time to do to the paperwork to renew my apartment, my mother was so angry. She was convinced that I was &ldquo;going to lose everything&rdquo; and she had screamed &ldquo;You think you&rsquo;re going to make money with your money on the NET?&rdquo; at me.</p>
<p>I love cryptography. Bitcoin was an interest then just as it was in 2013 and 2014. The attitude from my family regarding my interest Bitcoin in 2014 had caused me to say the weirdest thing. My professor had remembered it in 2019. I&rsquo;d say that &ldquo;I lost interest in Bitcoin because I need to be interested in every aspect of something to have a genuine interest in it.&rdquo; I&rsquo;d say &ldquo;I&rsquo;m interested in technology, but I&rsquo;m not interested in finances. Thus, I&rsquo;m not interested in Bitcoin.&rdquo; I&rsquo;ve never been brainwashed, but I&rsquo;ve been forced into complying.</p>
]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
