<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Prioritizing my Mental Health - Category - Steven Korvin</title>
        <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/categories/prioritizing-my-mental-health/</link>
        <description>Prioritizing my Mental Health - Category - Steven Korvin</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 18:40:43 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenkorvin.com/categories/prioritizing-my-mental-health/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Something to Let Out</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/something-to-let-out/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 18:40:43 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Steven Korvin</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/something-to-let-out/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>This is going to be a no holds barred post. In the past, I had worried about what my family might think regarding my posts about prioritizing my mental health.</p>
<p>I feel so much stress. This is not new. I have been feeling this for a very long time, perhaps, all my life. I&rsquo;m so fortunate to now have my own apartment. I just wish that I could drive. I don&rsquo;t wish that to have a social status or to hang out with friends. I don&rsquo;t wish it to go to events. I just wish that I wasn&rsquo;t trapped in my apartment.</p>
<p>For nine years, I had begged my parents for a car. Each time, I had gotten a new response. Each response was a deflection. Of course, one of those responses had been &ldquo;You want a car so bad? BUY ONE YOURSELF!&rdquo; After nine years, I did just that with an ABLE account. My mother&rsquo;s reaction to my car purchase had made me afraid for my life! After one day, I began looking to sell the car.</p>
<p>Please keep in mind that the car purchase was something that I had planned for months. It wasn&rsquo;t a spur of the moment decision. I worked for months to get my credit repaired. Getting my credit repaired involved many phone calls, a fax at Staples, and a trip to the hospital to receive my discharge papers. After my credit was repaired, I bought the car.</p>
<p>Going back a year prior, I had a once in a lifetime opportunity by getting FREE MONEY from my school. I ruined it. I don&rsquo;t care about most consumer items. It&rsquo;s not a philosophy. Most consumer items don&rsquo;t interest me. I bought such stupid things, though, and I repeated the process several times of buying and selling those items. The stress was unbearable.</p>
<p>The other component to my stress was that everything had felt so far away. I plan to apply to the Stevens Institute of Technology early next year and I still had a lot of difficult work to do to be able to apply. I had to take Pre-Calculus, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry, and Biology! Thankfully, I&rsquo;ve taken three of those classes and I&rsquo;ll be taking Chemistry this fall. That will allow me to apply early next year. I&rsquo;ve been trying so hard.</p>
<p>The circumstances that led me to get kicked out of NJIT no longer exist. I will be able to succeed at Stevens. I have my own apartment and I&rsquo;ve learned about my eligibility for the Total and Permanent Disability Discharge. Also, I&rsquo;ve been able to process all of the trauma from before I had left for NJIT.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s not just that I&rsquo;ve been stressed while doing nothing. I&rsquo;ve been working so hard. This is not a COVID-related issue. 2020 was very stressful for me, but it was an excellent year for me compared to other years. COVID had nothing to do with what I was feeling.</p>
<p>When I was at NJIT, I had taken Greyhounds in an attempt to deal with my stress. The Greyhounds had been very effective. When my mother had taken me out of the city and into the suburbs, I had felt such a relief. When I was at NJIT and when I was in the hospital, I had made a car the crux of my argument as to what could&rsquo;ve been done about my stress.</p>
<p>My brother had gotten a brand new Chevrolet Equinox as a graduation gift while I was stuck in my parents' house. Of course, my parents think that I&rsquo;m inhrerently unable to drive. My mother takes me out for drives nearly every day and that&rsquo;s done more than you can imagine for my stress.</p>
<p>My mother is under so much stress, too. If you put two and two together, wouldn&rsquo;t it be less stress for my mother if she had just my father to deal with? It&rsquo;s her choice to take me out for those drives, but she drives me to and from more pressing matters. She even cancels and postpones appointments to make that happen.</p>
<p>I had 1.44 BTC in April of 2020. It wasn&rsquo;t that I was shortsighted. I just couldn&rsquo;t take my stress. In February, I started getting to know my friend Asha who lives in central New Jersey. She has really helped as far as my stress has gone. Today, I saw news on Cointelegraph that Amazon plans to accept Bitcoin this year. Getting back to 1 BTC was a pipe dream.</p>
<p>I can&rsquo;t blame myself, but at the same time, this could&rsquo;ve been prevented. My mother&rsquo;s reactions in late 2019 hadn&rsquo;t helped, either. She had stolen my first school refund check! She had returned it after a month of pleading from me. Then, in December, when it was time to do to the paperwork to renew my apartment, my mother was so angry. She was convinced that I was &ldquo;going to lose everything&rdquo; and she had screamed &ldquo;You think you&rsquo;re going to make money with your money on the NET?&rdquo; at me.</p>
<p>I love cryptography. Bitcoin was an interest then just as it was in 2013 and 2014. The attitude from my family regarding my interest Bitcoin in 2014 had caused me to say the weirdest thing. My professor had remembered it in 2019. I&rsquo;d say that &ldquo;I lost interest in Bitcoin because I need to be interested in every aspect of something to have a genuine interest in it.&rdquo; I&rsquo;d say &ldquo;I&rsquo;m interested in technology, but I&rsquo;m not interested in finances. Thus, I&rsquo;m not interest in Bitcoin.&rdquo; I&rsquo;ve never been brainwashed, but I&rsquo;ve been forced into complying.</p>
]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>A Follow-Up to My Previous Post</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/a-follow-up-to-my-previous-post/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 10:45:57 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Steven Korvin</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/a-follow-up-to-my-previous-post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As I said in my first post, I dislike fiction. It&rsquo;s a story that I don&rsquo;t want 
to tell, but fiction was pretty much forced on me all my life. I live on my 
own now! Things are great! Shouldn&rsquo;t I have been able to disregard fiction as soon as I moved in to this apartment? The answer to that is &ldquo;No.&rdquo; I wasn&rsquo;t able to. When I first moved in here, I had no computer and no smartphone. I was at the library all day. The library was closed on Sundays during the summer, though. It was unbearable to stare at the walls all day.</p>
<p>Subscribing to 1Password after moving into this apartment had really helped me get things back in order. In August of 2019, I bought an iPhone SE. After the library would close, I&rsquo;d go to Starbucks. After Starbucks would close, I&rsquo;d be outside on some chairs using Optimum Wi-Fi until early hours of the morning. What I mean to say is that I&rsquo;d be outside on those chairs after running out of my phone plan&rsquo;s data allotment, which happened quickly.</p>
<p>My mother wasn&rsquo;t into helping me buy a refurbished ThinkPad. I&rsquo;m my own person, right? Thus, in September of 2019, I bought a used ThinkPad for $20. I stopped going to the library after that. In fact, I had to go to the library one last time after getting the laptop to create a Linux live CD. In September or October of 2019, I subscribed to Visible. Visible gave me unlimited hotspot data at 1.5 Mbps. It was very awkward when I had changed and forgotten my iPhone&rsquo;s lock screen passcode. I had to go to those chairs using Optimum Wi-Fi with my ThinkPad and my iPhone connected to it through USB to reflash iOS using iTunes.</p>
<p>Then, in October of 2019, I got my first refund check from school. I had given my mother the check after she had asked me for it. She didn&rsquo;t want to return the check after I had given her it! My mother was asking me &ldquo;why I had needed the money&rdquo; when &ldquo;I have everything that I need&rdquo; through my benefits. After a month of pleading from me, it was returned. I had to cash it at the bank branch that had serviced my school. I took an Uber there. Also, in December 2019, the paperwork had to be filled in to renew my apartment. My mother was convinced that it wasn&rsquo;t going to be renewed and she was very angry. These kinds of reactions had only served to mess with my mind further.</p>
<p>By spending my 1.44 BTC, I had actually made myself prepared for COVID. I bought a computer that I could do work on and I bought a wireless router. I had also subscribed to Spectrum for Internet service. I had a few months free as a college student, but they tacked on extra charges that I didn&rsquo;t ask for. It took a long phone call talking to three people who wanted me to sign up for Spectrum Mobile to get those charges removed.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve had plenty of opportunities to accumulate Bitcoin again since spending the 1.44 BTC, but I spent each time because of stress and my inability to give up fiction. Stress had contributed to my inability to give up fiction, but I was also cooped up in my apartment all day. My mother has been taking me for drives nearly every single day, which is very kind of her. I wish I could get out of here on my own time, though. What the hell am I supposed to do if I&rsquo;m in here all day, right? Well, I&rsquo;d consume fiction, which just made me feel sick. As I said in my first post, I had stopped with fiction after having something productive to do. That wasn&rsquo;t the only thing that got me to stop with fiction, though. I made an amazing friend in February of this year and having her around has sure helped me get past consuming fiction.</p>
<p>I suppose that feeling so far from my goal of applying to the Stevens Instutute of Technology had also contributed to my stress. In 2019, I learned that I had to take Pre-Calculus, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry, and Biology in order to best apply!</p>
<p>I will end this post by saying that it&rsquo;s very scary when you have no control over what you do. That awful, awful stress had left me with no control over what I had done. Hence, I can&rsquo;t really feel angry at myself because I had kept spending my Bitcoin. I didn&rsquo;t have control over my actions!</p>
]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Prioritizing Mental Health</title>
    <link>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/prioritizing-mental-health/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:22:42 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Steven Korvin</author>
    <guid>https://stevenkorvin.com/2021/07/prioritizing-mental-health/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As I just posted on my Hashnode blog, I need to stay occupied with things that are meaningful to me. I&rsquo;m doing QubitxQubit&rsquo;s Quantum Summer School held in collaboration with IBM on Monday to Friday from 12 to 4 pm. I&rsquo;m also taking a COBOL class at Bergen Community College, also held in collaboration with IBM, on Tuesdays and Thursdays from 7 to 9 pm. Additionally, I&rsquo;m continuing with the Electric Vehicle Conversion project and I&rsquo;ll be on campus on Tuesdays and Wednesdays from 9 to 11 am. These things are all very healthy for me and they&rsquo;re things that I want to do.</p>
<p>In April of 2020, I had 1.44 BTC. How can I possibly HODL when I&rsquo;m as stressed as I was? I spent it all in one night. COVID had nothing to do with that &ldquo;mistake.&rdquo; I was just feeling so much stress. I tried to do something about my stress and in November of 2020, I bought a car knowing that I wasn&rsquo;t going to be able to pay for gas and insurance. I ended up selling the car.</p>
<p>I was about to start a data science menteeship with a mentor from MentorCruise. I suddenly became very busy, though, and I felt that it would be better for me to take things at my own pace.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m going to be prioritizing my mental health by staying productive.</p>
]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
